https://orcabayfoods.com/privacy-policy/

Orca Bay Seafoods, Inc. (“Orca Bay Seafoods“) operates orcabayseafoods.com and may operate other websites. It is Orca Bay’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
WEBSITE VISITORS
Like most website operators, Orca Bay Seafoods collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Orca Bay’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Orca Bay’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Orca Bay Seafoods may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Orca Bay Seafoods also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on orcabayseafoods.com blogs/sites. Orca Bay Seafoods only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.
GATHERING OF PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION
Certain visitors to Orca Bay’s websites choose to interact with Orca Bay Seafoods in ways that require Orca Bay Seafoods to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Orca Bay Seafoods gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at orcabayseafoods.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Orca Bay Seafoods are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Orca Bay Seafoods collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Orca Bay Seafoods. Orca Bay Seafoods does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
AGGREGATED STATISTICS
Orca Bay Seafoods may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Orca Bay Seafoods may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Orca Bay Seafoods does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
PROTECTION OF CERTAIN PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION
Orca Bay Seafoods discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Orca Bay’s behalf or to provide services available at Orca Bay’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Orca Bay’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Orca Bay Seafoods will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Orca Bay Seafoods discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Orca Bay Seafoods believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Orca Bay Seafoods, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Orca Bay Seafoods website and have supplied your email address, Orca Bay Seafoods may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Orca Bay Seafoods and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Orca Bay Seafoods takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
COOKIES
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Orca Bay Seafoods uses cookies to help Orca Bay Seafoods identify and track visitors, their usage of Orca Bay Seafoods website, and their website access preferences. Orca Bay Seafoods visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Orca Bay’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Orca Bay’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
BUSINESS TRANSFERS
If Orca Bay Seafoods, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Orca Bay Seafoods goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Orca Bay Seafoods may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
ADS
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Orca Bay Seafoods and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Orca Bay Seafoods may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Orca Bay’s sole discretion. Orca Bay Seafoods encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a orcabayseafoods.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Home
Seafood Products
Find In-Store
Recipes
Culture
Learn
News
Contact
